http://www.dipra.com/privacy-policy

HomeAbout UsAbout UsMember CompaniesAlliancesEnvironmental PolicyDuctile Iron Pipe BenefitsDuctile Iron Pipe BenefitsAbout Ductile Iron PipeCentury ClubIron Pipe TestimonialsThe Pipeline: News From DIPRAFlow Test of 97-Year-Old Cement-Mortar Lined PipeHighlights of Polyethylene Encasement InvestigationThe Truth About Cement-Mortar Lined PipeDIPRA Facts & FiguresBenefits of Ductile Iron PipeDuctile Iron versus PVCDuctile Iron versus SteelEnvironmental BenefitsSustainable Pipe CertificationThe Truth About EPDsV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement V-Bio Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement PatentsBonded Coatings versus Polyethylene EncasementBuried No LongerCorrosion ControlDangers of Using PVCResourcesCalculatorsDesign on SupportsHydraulic Analysis/Greenhouse GasThickness DesignThrust RestraintLife Cycle Cost Analysis
Downloadable BrochuresBenefitsCelebrate Sustainable InfrastructureInside Pipe DiameterLife Cycle Cost AnalysisV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene EncasementTechnical PublicationsALL Technical Publications (List)GeneralFeaturesApplicationsDesignHydraulicsTappingGuidelinesMaterial ComparisonsPipe StandardsHistoricalFrench Technical PublicationsCorrosion ControlFAQsDesignCorrosion ControlHydraulicsThrust RestraintInstallationTappingManufacturingSubstitute Materials
Other ResourcesAsk an EngineerOrder Installation Guides
Videos/WebinarsFlow Test of 97-Year-Old Cement-Mortar Lined PipeCentury ClubThe Smart, Sustainable SolutionV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement InstallationWebinarsAdvocacyAdvocacyLocal ChoiceWrite Your RepresentativeNews & EventsNews, Opinions and CommentaryWhere We Are - Upcoming EventsACE Pipe Tapping ActionDIPRA Media KitCareersContact UsDIPRA StaffRegional EngineersAsk an EngineerMember Login
Privacy Policy
Strength and Durability for Life®
HomeAbout UsAbout UsMember CompaniesAlliancesEnvironmental PolicyDuctile Iron Pipe BenefitsDuctile Iron Pipe BenefitsAbout Ductile Iron PipeCentury ClubIron Pipe TestimonialsThe Pipeline: News From DIPRAFlow Test of 97-Year-Old Cement-Mortar Lined PipeHighlights of Polyethylene Encasement InvestigationThe Truth About Cement-Mortar Lined PipeDIPRA Facts & FiguresBenefits of Ductile Iron PipeDuctile Iron versus PVCDuctile Iron versus SteelEnvironmental BenefitsSustainable Pipe CertificationThe Truth About EPDsV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement V-Bio Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement PatentsBonded Coatings versus Polyethylene EncasementBuried No LongerCorrosion ControlDangers of Using PVCResourcesCalculatorsDesign on SupportsHydraulic Analysis/Greenhouse GasThickness DesignThrust RestraintLife Cycle Cost AnalysisDownloadable BrochuresBenefitsCelebrate Sustainable InfrastructureInside Pipe DiameterLife Cycle Cost AnalysisV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene EncasementTechnical PublicationsALL Technical Publications (List)GeneralFeaturesApplicationsDesignHydraulicsTappingGuidelinesMaterial ComparisonsPipe StandardsHistoricalFrench Technical PublicationsCorrosion ControlFAQsDesignCorrosion ControlHydraulicsThrust RestraintInstallationTappingManufacturingSubstitute MaterialsOther ResourcesAsk an EngineerOrder Installation GuidesVideos/WebinarsFlow Test of 97-Year-Old Cement-Mortar Lined PipeCentury ClubThe Smart, Sustainable SolutionV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement InstallationWebinarsAdvocacyAdvocacyLocal ChoiceWrite Your RepresentativeNews & EventsNews, Opinions and CommentaryWhere We Are - Upcoming EventsACE Pipe Tapping ActionDIPRA Media KitCareersContact UsDIPRA StaffRegional EngineersAsk an EngineerMember Login
Search ...
Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association Website Privacy Statement
Print
Email
Effective Date: This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 19, 2012.
1. ACKNOWLEDGMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS
Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association (collectively "we", or "us") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when a visitor (collectively "user", or "you", or "your computer") interacts with our website. By accessing DIPRA.org, you acknowledge and fully understand Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in the Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association Privacy Statement.
2. INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW IT IS USED
DIPRA.org collects certain information from and about its users in different ways: directly from our Web Server logs, with Cookies, the user and other technologies, including, but not limited to, javascript.
a. Web Server Logs.
When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include (but are not limited to):
Your Internet protocol address.
The kind of browser or computer you use.
Number of links you click within the site.
Location-specific information such as the State or country from which you accessed the site.
Date and time of your visit.
Name of your Internet service provider.
Web page you linked to our site from.
Pages you viewed on the site.
This information may be shared with partners of the Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association and other third parties including, but not limited to analytics providers, email service providers and ad networks.
b. Use of Cookies
DIPRA.org may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.
Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association reserves the right to share site statistics and visitor data with partner companies and to allow other companies and partners to place third-party cookies on our website. Such reasons for third-party cookies include, but are not limited to, circumstances where there is a temporary, overriding customer value or behavioral ad tracking.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.
c. Personal Information Users
Visitors to our website can register to use or purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider or credit card payment processor. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting. You may also be asked to take part in an online survey, in which you would disclose relevant information to questions we ask.
We may choose to disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission, including but not limited to:
To fulfill your service requests for services,
To someone you have assigned to act on your behalf, such as an agent.
To a limited amount to our employees, affiliates, partners, consultants, contractors, service providers, suppliers, agents, subsidiaries and any other persons acting on our behalf,
To protect ourselves from liability,
To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.
We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address.
Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).
We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.
To customize our website, service and other offerings for you, we and our partners may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer or device. This location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used only to provide and improve our service. We may obtain your consent on your first use of the service.
We may keep data indefinitely.
California residents are legally entitled (at no charge and no more than once annually) to request information about how we may have shared your information with others for direct marketing purposes. Contact us for this information:
Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association 2000 2nd Avenue, South Suite 429 Birmingham, AL 35233 United States Phone: (205) 402-8700
Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity. Click to see company privacy policies and opt-out choices:
In order to serve you, we may share your personal and anonymous information with other companies, including vendors and contractors. Their use of information is limited to these purposes, and subject to agreements that require them to keep the information confidential. Our vendors provide assurance that they take reasonable steps to safeguard the data they hold on our behalf, although data security cannot be guaranteed.
Analytics companies may access data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data.
We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.
Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.
To customize our service for you, we and our partners may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer or device. This location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used only to provide and improve our service. We may obtain your consent on your first use of the service.
We may share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with trusted partners in order to provide you with relevant advertising, offers or services.
Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity. Click to see company privacy policies and opt-out choices:
We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.
Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.
d. Other Technologies; Javascript
When you visit our website, we may from time to time record your viewing session using a technology called Javascript, which is common code found in a Web Page. Such recordings can save the scrolling and mouse pointer activity within the viewport of the web browser you use to access our website. Such recordings may be shared with third party analytics vendors for the purposes of web usability improvements and testing. These recordings may contain identifiable information, including, but not limited to, your IP address, operating system and access times.
3. SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
DIPRA.org will make every effort to ensure the safekeeping and security of all visitors personal information.
4. CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT
Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "updated" date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
5. CONTACTING US
If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. You may also write to us at:
Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association 2000 2nd Avenue, South Suite 429 Birmingham, AL 35233 United States Phone: (205) 402-8700
Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.Twitter
HomeAbout UsAbout UsMember CompaniesAlliancesEnvironmental PolicyDuctile Iron Pipe BenefitsDuctile Iron Pipe BenefitsAbout Ductile Iron PipeCentury ClubIron Pipe TestimonialsThe Pipeline: News From DIPRAFlow Test of 97-Year-Old Cement-Mortar Lined PipeHighlights of Polyethylene Encasement InvestigationThe Truth About Cement-Mortar Lined PipeDIPRA Facts & FiguresBenefits of Ductile Iron PipeDuctile Iron versus PVCDuctile Iron versus SteelEnvironmental BenefitsSustainable Pipe CertificationThe Truth About EPDsV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement V-Bio Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement PatentsBonded Coatings versus Polyethylene EncasementBuried No LongerCorrosion ControlDangers of Using PVCResourcesCalculatorsDesign on SupportsHydraulic Analysis/Greenhouse GasThickness DesignThrust RestraintLife Cycle Cost AnalysisDownloadable BrochuresBenefitsCelebrate Sustainable InfrastructureInside Pipe DiameterLife Cycle Cost AnalysisV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene EncasementTechnical PublicationsALL Technical Publications (List)GeneralFeaturesApplicationsDesignHydraulicsTappingGuidelinesMaterial ComparisonsPipe StandardsHistoricalFrench Technical PublicationsCorrosion ControlFAQsDesignCorrosion ControlHydraulicsThrust RestraintInstallationTappingManufacturingSubstitute MaterialsOther ResourcesAsk an EngineerOrder Installation GuidesVideos/WebinarsFlow Test of 97-Year-Old Cement-Mortar Lined PipeCentury ClubThe Smart, Sustainable SolutionV-Bio® Enhanced Polyethylene Encasement InstallationWebinarsAdvocacyAdvocacyLocal ChoiceWrite Your RepresentativeNews & EventsNews, Opinions and CommentaryWhere We Are - Upcoming EventsACE Pipe Tapping ActionDIPRA Media KitCareersContact UsDIPRA StaffRegional EngineersAsk an EngineerMember Login
Benefits ofDuctile Iron Pipe
A century ago, dedicated American engineers installed iron pipe to create the country’s water systems.This strong, safe, and reliable product has stood the test of time.
Read More
Technical Publications
Read More
You are here:
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Strength and Durability for Life®
Home
About Us
Ductile Iron Pipe Benefits
Technical Publications
Calculators
Advocacy
News & Events
Contact Us
P.O. Box 190306Birmingham, AL 35219205.402.8700 Tel Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Privacy Policy | Site Map | Contact Us    © Copyright 2020 Ductile Iron Pipe Research Association
